(Penny:)Yup, that's good.
(Penny:)Wine glasses should have handles.
(Amy:)Keeping accurate track
of your alcohol intake.
(Amy:)Smart idea, considering how trampy
you get when you've had a few.
(Penny:)You heard what I did?
- Well, I heard who you did.
- Ugh.
(Penny:)Oh, my God, I screwed up everything.
(Penny:)I hurt Leonard, I hurt Raj.
I mean, what is wrong with me?
(Penny:)I feel like two totally different people.
(Penny:)Dr. Jekyll and Mrs. Whore.
Don't be so hard on yourseIf.
(Amy:)- Know the story of Catherine the Great?
- No.
She ruled Russia in the late 1700s, and
one night when she was feeling randy...
(Amy:)...she used an intricate system of pulleys
to have intimate relations with a horse.
(Howard:)I'm sorry,
what does this have to do with me?
(Amy:)She engaged
in inter-species hanky-panky...
(Amy:)...and people still call her great.
(Amy:)I'm sure your reputation can survive
you shagging a Iittle lndian boy.